https://www.mandarins.org/about/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - Sacramento Mandarins
Skip to content
Menu
Menu HomeAboutMenu ToggleWho We AreDirector’s MessageBoard of DirectorsHistoryPolicy HandbookPrivacy PolicyWhistleblowerProgramsMenu ToggleMandarins Drum CorpsMenu ToggleAuditionMenu ToggleBecome a MemberAudition InformationAnswers for ParentsMember HubMenu ToggleExperience Camp DetailsShuttle FormPaymentsAnnouncementsCorpsDataMeet the StaffMember HandbookPayment ScheduleMail DropsStaffMenu ToggleAdministrative StaffDesign StaffInstructional StaffSupport StaffScores and ReviewsMenu Toggle2019 Scores & Reviews2018 Scores & ReviewsPerformance ScheduleMandarins Music AcademyMenu ToggleFall Clinic SeriesSummer CampsElementary School Music ProgramsLesson StudioMandarins EntertainmentMenu ToggleGalleryPerformance ScheduleShopSupportMenu ToggleDonateMenu ToggleDonate Now!Donor Bill of RightsGiving LevelsScholarship DriveTour SponsorshipMenu ToggleTour Sponsorship FormTour Sponsorship Online FormFriends of the MandarinsVolunteerCorporate PartnersBingoEventsMenu ToggleDCI Capital ClassicCalendarNewsAlumniMenu ToggleAlumni Stories50th Anniversary DVDContact Us
Search for:
Home / About / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Effective date: September 15, 2018Mandarins of Sacramento Inc. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the www.mandarins.org website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. Our Privacy Policy for Mandarins of Sacramento Inc. is managed through Free Privacy Policy.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from www.mandarins.org.
Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last namePhone numberAddress, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, CityCookies and Usage DataUsage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies.  We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies.  We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies.  We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Usage of DataMandarins of Sacramento Inc. uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain the ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer care and supportTo provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the ServiceTo monitor the usage of the ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.Mandarins of Sacramento Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of DataLegal RequirementsMandarins of Sacramento Inc. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of Mandarins of Sacramento Inc.To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liability
Security of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google AnalyticsGoogle Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Links to Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By visiting this page on our website: http://www.mandarins.org/contact
PROGRAMSDrum CorpsMandarins Music AcademyMandarins EntertainmentABOUTWho We AreDirector’s MessageBoard of DirectorsHistoryPolicy HandbookPrivacy PolicyWhistleblowerSUPPORTDonateFeed the KidsFriends of the MandarinsCorporate PartnersVolunteerShopALUMNIAlumni DirectoryAlumni AssociationCONTACT US Subscribe to our newsletter Subscribe to our newsletter and stay up-to-date on all the latest Mandarins, Alumni, Bingo news & events.
First Name Last Name Email
Subscribe
Facebook
Twitter
Youtube
Vimeo
Instagram
Rss
Copyright © 2020 Website owned and maintained by Mandarins of Sacramento, Inc. Box 22297 - Sacramento, CA 95822 • A not-for-profit youth organization
Scroll to Top
20% off
SHOP
discount code: FANDARINS20
We would like your feedback on our new website!
Let us know what you think
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
got it
